

Krishna K. Keshri

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

+91-8553192768

Arrah, Bihar

keshri819@gmail.com

krishna-keshri.vercel.app

in @krishna-kumar-keshri

@KrishnaKumarKeshri96

PROFILE

A passionate and driven learner. Full-stack web developer with specialization in MERN stack and ability to write clean, reusable, and optimized code. Skilled and experienced in building and maintaining MERN-based web applications. Looking forward to working in a challenging and progressive work environment.

SKILLS

- Javascript
- ReactJS
- Redux
- HTML
- CSS
- NodeJS
- ExpressJS
- MongoDB
- Data Structures & Algorithms

EDUCATION HISTORY

Full-Stack Web Development

Masai School 04/2021 – 09/2021 | Online

Bachelor of Hotel Management

Ramaiah University 2014 – 2018 | Bangalore

PROJECTS

Cult.fit clone 🗘 🔗

Fitness megastore platform Cultfit using MERN stack as a part of learning curve in Masai School.

Features:

- End-to-end product purchasing flow within the "store section".
- Buying subscription and booking a trial workout session from cult.fit.

Tech Stack: CSS | React | Node | Express | MongoDB **Areas of responsibility:**

- Developed end-to-end product purchasing flow within the "store section".
- Contributed to database and logic integration for the user experience and fetching products from the backend.
- Integrated with the backend using MongoDB

A collaborative project, built in 5 days by a team of 4 developers and 2 designers.

Internshala Clone 👩 🔗

An online platform that lists internships and training programs.

Features:

- Sign-in/sign-up
- Search bar to search Internships in a domain of user's choice
- Multiple filters to filter Internships (price, location, etc.)

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | Javascript | Node | Express | MongoDB **Areas of responsibility:**

- Developed the Sign-in/Sign-up pages
- Laid out database schema and built the REST API for the same.
- Developed the dynamic 'details' page of the listed Internship.

A collaborative project built by a team of 3, executed in 4 days.

Covid-Stats 🗘 🔗

An overview of the damage caused by Covid-19 in the form of maps and charts.

Features:

- Select a country by clicking on map
- Number of cases country-wise sorting potion
- Decent UI

Tech Stack: SCSS| React

A solo project developed in a day.

WORK EXPERIENCE

INSTRUCTIONAL ASSOCIATE | DEVELOPER

Masai School

Oct 2021 - Present

- Solve conceptual doubts of students.
- Assisting faculty members with assignment supervision.
- Organizing technical sessions (DSA, Coding) for students whenever required.
- Contributing to the internal and industry projects of Masai.

ASSISTANT RESTAURANT MANAGER

KFC - Bengaluru

2018 - 2021

- Ensured whether the ordering of raw material is done as per consumption and received as per SOP i.e., meeting TTCS (Time &Temperature Control for Safety).
- Maintained budget and employee records, checked payroll, pay bills, and monitored records.
- Managed daily restaurant operations and assisted with product planning, forecasting, maintaining sanitation standards and plan labor hours.